Finding Aid for the Peter H. Prince Papers MS.2921
University of Tennessee Libraries, Special Collections
- Research Files, 1770-2006; I
  - Photographs, 1838-2006 (bulk 1884-2005); J
    - Greenbriar Cove: Smoky Mountains Hiking Club Collection, 1935 (Box 36, Folder 38)
    - Greenbriar Cove: Laurel School, 1907, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 39)
    - Greenbriar Cove: Granny's College, 1922, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 40)
    - Greenbriar Cove: Great Smoky Mountains Hiking Club Cabin, 1951 March 17-18 (Box 36, Folder 41)
    - Greenbriar Cove: Greenbriar Pinnacle (Looking Toward Mount LeConte), 1928 (Box 36, Folder 42)
    - Greenbriar Cove: Unidentified Grave, 1987 August 20 (Box 36, Folder 43)
    - Greenbriar Cove: Greenbriar Pinnacle, 1926 (Box 36, Folder 44)
    - Greenbriar Cove: M. A. Low Slate Headstone, 1995 May 16 (Box 36, Folder 45)
    - Greenbriar Cove: Luther Christianberry Parton, circa 1910s (Box 36, Folder 46)
    - Greenbriar Cove: Greenbriar Hotel, undated (Box 36, Folder 47)
    - Greenbriar Cove: LeConte Hotel, circa 1927 (Box 36, Folder 48)
    - Greenbriar Cove: Ramsay Cascades Hotel, 1946, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 49)
    - Greenbriar Cove: CCC Camp David C. Chapman, 1933 November 19 (Box 36, Folder 50)
    - Greenbriar Cove: Dolly Parton Statue, 1996 May 27, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 51)
    - Greenbriar Cove: Chris Parton, 1911, 2001; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 89, Folder 1] (Box 36, Folder 52)
    - Greenbriar Cove: Dolly Parton Visits Smoky Mountains Relatives, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 53)
    - Greenbriar Cove: Dolly Parton Statue, 1996 March 12 (Box 36, Folder 54)
    - Greenbriar Cove: Chris Parton, 1911 (Box 36, Folder 55)
    - Greenbriar Cove: Chris Parton Cemetery, 1987 July 13 (Box 36, Folder 56)
    - Greenbriar Cove: Chris Parton Cemetery, 1987 July 13 (Box 36, Folder 57)
    - Greenbriar Cove: Chris Parton Grave, 2002 November 30 (Box 36, Folder 58)
    - Pittman Center: Emert Cove Bridge, 2003 February 12 (Box 36, Folder 59)
    - Pittman Center: Pittman Center Methodist Church, 1920 (Box 36, Folder 60)
    - Pittman Center: John Rungen Memorial Methodist Episcopal Church, circa 1924 (Box 36, Folder 61)
    - Pittman Center: Thomas Frasure Pension Application, 1905 December 18 (Box 36, Folder 62)
    - Pittman Center: Pittman Center Methodist Center Namesake Eli Pittman, undated (Box 36, Folder 63)
    - Pittman Center: Sergeant Thomas Frasure Grave, 1996 November 11 (Box 36, Folder 64)
    - Lindsey Mill: Richard G. Wright Grave, undated (Box 36, Folder 65)
    - Lindsey Mill: Reverend John W. Lindsey Grave, undated (Box 36, Folder 66)
    - Lindsey Mill: Isaac Lindsey Overshot Mill, 1940 August 4 (Box 36, Folder 67)
    - Lindsey Mill: Isaac Lindsey Overshot Mill, 1940 August 4 (Box 36, Folder 68)
    - Lindsey Mill: Isaac Lindsey Mill (Interior), 1940 August 3 (Box 36, Folder 69)
    - Lindsey Mill: Isaac Lindsey Overshot Mill, 1936 October 15 (Box 36, Folder 70)
    - Lindsey Mill: Isaac Lindsey Overshot Mill, 1936 November 15 (Box 36, Folder 71)
    - Lindsey Mill: Isaac Lindsey Mill (Interior), 1940, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 72)
    - Lindsey Mill: Evans Chapel Methodist Episcopal Church, 1942 January, 1977 September 29, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 73)
    - Copeland Creek: Two White Cap Murderers Hanged, 1899 July 5 (Box 36, Folder 74)
    - Copeland Creek: Lizzie Chandler, undated (Box 36, Folder 75)
    - Copeland Creek: Laura Whaley, undated (Box 36, Folder 76)
    - Copeland Creek: Dr. Jerome Russell, undated (Box 36, Folder 77)
    - Copeland Creek: Middle Copeland Creek Frame House, 1940 January (Box 36, Folder 78)
    - Copeland Creek: Bonwell's Chapel Methodist Episcopal Church North, 1940 January (Box 36, Folder 79)
    - Copeland Creek: Nancy J. McCarter Slate Gravestone, undated (Box 36, Folder 80)
    - Copeland Creek: Mitchell Parton Slate, 1987 October 31 (Box 36, Folder 81)
    - Copeland Creek: McCager Rector Slate Gravestone, undated (Box 36, Folder 82)
    - Jones Cove: Mitchell Ramsey Overshot Mill, 1935 September 23 (Box 36, Folder 83)
    - Jones Cove: James P. Ramsey House, 1953 (Box 36, Folder 84)
    - Jones Cove: Tyson M. McCarter House, 1936 December 16 (Box 36, Folder 85)
    - Cosby: Horace Albright, 2006 (Box 36, Folder 86)
    - Cosby: Arno Cammerer, 2006 (Box 36, Folder 87)
    - Cosby: Maddron Bald (5212'), 1947 February 2 (Box 36, Folder 88)
    - Cosby: Reverend Lawson Maddron (1808-1896), undated, 2000; [Oversized Items Removed to Box 89, Folder 2] (Box 36, Folder 89)
    - Cosby: Lawson Maddron Grave, 2004 March 19 (Box 36, Folder 90)
    - Cosby: Lawson Maddron Grave, 2004 March 19 (Box 36, Folder 91)
    - Cosby: Dr. James Cozby Grave, undated (Box 36, Folder 92)
    - Cosby: Sandra A. Proffit with Ramp (Vegetable), 1956 May 6 (Box 36, Folder 93)
    - Cosby: Mrs. Albert Carver House, 1937-1942 (Box 36, Folder 94)
    - Cosby: Alex Baxter Cabin, 1937, 1987 July 10 (Box 36, Folder 95)
    - Cosby: Sallie Sutton Grave, 1997 May 17 (Box 36, Folder 96)
    - Cosby: Allen Jenkins (Moonshiner), 1932 (Box 36, Folder 97)
    - Cosby: Ollie M. Caton Grave, 1987; [No Photograph] (Box 36, Folder 98)
    - Cosby: Lieutenant McKinney McMahan Sr. Gravesite (no photograph), 1987 June 26 (Box 36, Folder 99)
    - Cosby: McKinney McMahan Gravesite, 2004 March 26 (Box 36, Folder 100)
    - Cosby: Mountain Rest School, 1937 March 22 (Box 36, Folder 101)
    - Cosby: Sally Carver Gravesite, 1997 May 17 (Box 36, Folder 102)
    - Cosby: Ella V. Costner, undated (Box 36, Folder 103)
    - Cosby: Ella V. Costner Gravesite, 2004 March 28 (Box 36, Folder 104)
    - Cosby: Lusindy Carver Gravesite, 1997 May 17 (Box 36, Folder 105)
    - Cosby: John Henry Spider Sutton Gravesite, 2004 March 28 (Box 36, Folder 106)
    - Cosby: Willis Baxter Cabin (no photo), undated (Box 36, Folder 107)
    - Cosby: John H. Campbell Grist Mill, 1996 November 4 (Box 36, Folder 108)
    - Cosby: Isaac L. Ogle Gravesite, 1997 May 17 (Box 36, Folder 109)
    - Cosby: Allen Sutton Cabin, 1926, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 110)
    - Cosby: Lucynda Campbell Benson House, undated; [No Photograph] (Box 36, Folder 111)
    - Cosby: Cosby Post Office, 1933 (Box 36, Folder 112)
    - Cosby: Mountain Rest School, circa 1926 (Box 36, Folder 113)
    - Cosby: Plowing, 1936 April 12; [No Photograph] (Box 36, Folder 114)
    - Cosby: Farming, 1936 April 12 (Box 36, Folder 115)
    - Cosby: Tobe Phillips Cabin, 1936 June 14, 1981, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 116)
    - Cosby: Reverend Thomas Caton Cabin, 2004 March 28 (Box 36, Folder 117)
    - Cosby: John H. Campbell Gravesite, 1997 May 17 (Box 36, Folder 118)
    - Cosby: John Campbell Overshot Grist Mill, 1936 June 5 (Box 36, Folder 119)
    - Cosby: Arno B. Cammerer, undated (Box 36, Folder 120)
    - Cosby: Horace M. Albright, undated (Box 36, Folder 121)
    - Cosby: First Plane Crash in the Smokies, 1922 November, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 122)
    - Cosby: Rachel Florence Fowler, 1987 July 9; [No Photograph] (Box 36, Folder 123)
    - Cosby: Hannah Cemetery, undated; [No Photograph] (Box 36, Folder 124)
    - Cosby: Jennifer Grave, undated (Box 36, Folder 125)
    - Cosby: Sawmill Boiler Ruins, 1987 September 14; [No Photograph] (Box 36, Folder 126)
    - Cosby: Elder Isaac Lemon Ogle, undated; [No Photograph] (Box 36, Folder 127)
    - Cosby: Alex Webb Gravestone, undated; [No Photograph] (Box 36, Folder 128)
    - Cosby: Campbell Cemetery, 1989 April 18; [No Photograph] (Box 36, Folder 129)
    - Cosby: Bill Proffitt Apple Barn, 1953 February (Box 36, Folder 130)
    - Cosby: Reverend Leroy L. Brown House, 1950 November 1 (Box 36, Folder 131)
    - Cosby: Mountain Rest School Class, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 132)
    - Cosby: Tom Dorsey (Merchant) Gravesite, 1996 November 4 (Box 36, Folder 133)
    - Cosby: Mountain Rest Primitive Baptist Church, undated (Box 36, Folder 134)
    - Cosby: Tobe Phillips, 2004 March 19 (Box 36, Folder 135)
    - Cosby: Jonas Tobe Phillips Grave, 1987 June 24 (Box 36, Folder 136)
    - Cosby: Dr. Lawson Maddron, 2000 March 24 (Box 36, Folder 137)
    - Other: Rocky Point Ferry Cabin, circa 1896, 1991; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 89, Folder 3] (Box 36, Folder 138)
    - Other: James Monroe Rymer and Family, undated (Box 36, Folder 139)
    - Other: James M. Rymer Gravesite, 1988, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 140)
    - Other: Rocky Point (Rymer's) Ferry, undated (Box 36, Folder 141)
    - Other: Rymer's Ferry, 1908; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 89, Folder 4] (Box 36, Folder 142)
    - Other: Robert Henderson's Lower Meeting House, undated; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 90, Folder 1] (Box 36, Folder 143)
    - Other: Unidentified Structures, undated (Box 36, Folder 144)
    - Other: Unidentified Trains, undated (Box 36, Folder 145)
    - Other: Unidentified Vistas, undated; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 90, Folder 2] (Box 36, Folder 146)
    - Reformatted Unidentified Negatives: A, circa 1950s (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Reformatted Unidentified Negatives: B, circa 1950s (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Reformatted Unidentified Negatives: Buildings, circa 1950s (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Reformatted Unidentified Negatives: C, circa 1950s (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Reformatted Unidentified Negatives: D, circa 1950s (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Reformatted Unidentified Negatives: F, circa 1950s (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Reformatted Unidentified Negatives: G, circa 1950s (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Reformatted Unidentified Negatives: H, circa 1950s (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Reformatted Unidentified Negatives: J, circa 1950s (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Reformatted Unidentified Negatives: K, circa 1950s (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Reformatted Unidentified Negatives: L, circa 1950s (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Reformatted Unidentified Negatives: M, circa 1950s (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Reformatted Unidentified Negatives: N-O, circa 1950s (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Reformatted Unidentified Negatives: P, circa 1950s (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Reformatted Unidentified Negatives: R, circa 1950s (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Reformatted Unidentified Negatives: S, circa 1950s (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Reformatted Unidentified Negatives: T, circa 1950s (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Reformatted Unidentified Negatives: V, circa 1950s (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Reformatted Unidentified Negatives: W, circa 1950s (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Reformatted Unidentified Negatives: Y, circa 1950s (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - CD of Reformatted Unidentified Negatives, circa 1950s (Box 37, Folder 21)
      File Specifications
      These images are 300 dpi .jpg files and require a computer with a CD drive to view.
  - Maps, 1883-2005; K
    - World Map, 1993; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 90, Folder 7] (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Tennessee - North Carolina Quadrangle Composite, 1940; [Removed to Box 91] (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Tennessee Quadrangles, 1940-1991; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 90, Folder 8 and Box 92] (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Tennessee Quadrangles Damaged by Mold, 1940-1991; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 93, Folder 1] (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Other Tennessee Maps, 1876-2002; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 90, Folder 9 and Map Storage] (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - North Carolina Quadrangles, 1940-2000; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 90, Folder 10] (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - North Carolina Quadrangles Damaged by Mold, 1940-2000; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 93, Folder 2] (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - North Carolina Quadrangles (duplicate), 1935-1936; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 90, Folder 11] (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Other North Carolina Maps, 1833-1932, 2000; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 94, Folder 1] (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Tennessee-North Carolina Quadrangles, 1884-1997; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 94, Folder 2 and Map Storage] (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Tennessee-North Carolina and North Carolina-Tennessee Quadrangles Damaged by Mold, 1884-1997; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 93, Folder 3] (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - North Carolina-Georgia Quadrangle, 1988; [Removed to Box 94, Folder 3] (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Maps of the Great Smoky Mountains National Park, 1886-1995; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 94, Folder 4] (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Maps of TVA Holdings, 1943 March-April, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Maps of Company Holdings, 1906-1943; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 94, Folder 5] (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Maps of Discrete Locations and Trails, 1972-2003; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 94, Folder 6] (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Maps of California, 2000-2001; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 95, Folder 1] (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Maps of Florida, 1988-2001; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 95, Folder 2] (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Maps of New Jersey, 2000-2001; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 95, Folder 3] (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Maps of Virginia and Surrounding States, 1997-2005; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 95, Folder 4] (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Maps of other U. S. States and Canadian Provinces, 1987-2005; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 95, Folder 5] (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Maps of Foreign Countries, 2000-2005; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 95, Folder 6] (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Reference Publications, 1883-2006 (bulk 1945-2006); L
    - 20,001 Names for Baby, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Abraham Jobe Autobiography, 1893-1905; (1 of 2) (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Abraham Jobe Autobiography, 1893-1905; (2 of 2) (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - The Admission of Tennessee into the Union by Samuel C. Williams, 1945-1988 (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - Alaska: Official State Vacation Planner, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - American Indians: A Select Catalog of National Archives Microfilm Publications (2nd Ed.), 1995 (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - Index to Anderson County Records (partial), 1975 (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - The Associated Press Stylebook and Libel Manual, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - List of Bedford County Court Documents (partial), undated (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - Beck & Phillips Families [of] North Carolina & Tennessee, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 32)
    - 1880 Census of Bedford County, Tennessee, 1978; [Transcription] (Box 38, Folder 33)
    - 1850 Census of Blount County, Tennessee, 1988; [Transcription] (Box 38, Folder 34)
    - 1860 Census of Blount County, Tennessee, 1981; [Transcription] (Box 38, Folder 35)
    - 1880 Census of Blount County, Tennessee, undated; [Transcription] (Box 38, Folder 36)
    - 1900 Census of Blount County, Tennessee, 1995; [Partial Transcription] (Box 38, Folder 37)
    - The Bone Rattler, 2002-2003 (Box 38, Folder 38)
    - A Brief History of the Great Smoky Mountains National Park Movement in North Carolina, 1940 (Box 38, Folder 39)
    - Brief History of Tapoco and the Great Smoky Country, 1954 May (Box 38, Folder 40)
    - Bryson City Capital of Swain County, circa 1973 (Box 38, Folder 41)
    - Cades Cove Methodist Episcopal Church, South, Membership Rolls (Incomplete), 1855-1903, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 42)
    - Call Me Hillbilly, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 43)
    - Campaign for a National Park in Western North Carolina, 1885-1940, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 44)
    - Casper Cable and Descendants, 1755-1990, 1991; (Item Housed Loose in Box) (Box 38, Folder 45)
    - Catalog of Publications, Tennessee Division of Geology, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 46)
    - Cataloochee: Lost Settlement of the Smokies, 1982; (1 of 2) (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Cataloochee: Lost Settlement of the Smokies, 1982; (2 of 2) (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - The Cemeteries of Swain County, North Carolina, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - The Cemeteries of Swain County, North Carolina, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Central United Methodist Church Directory, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Cherokee Landmarks Around the Great Smokies, 1950 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - The Cherokees of the Smoky Mountains, 1936 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Cherokee Trail of Tears, 1950-1962; (1 of 2) (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Cherokee Trail of Tears, 1950-1962; (2 of 2) (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Cherokee Treaties and Records, undated (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Cherokee Words With Pictures, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Church Street United Methodist Church Directory, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Church Street United Methodist Church Directory, 2002-2003 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - 1850 Population Schedule for Cocke County, Tennessee, 1983; [Transcription] (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - 1860 Population Schedule for Cocke County, Tennessee, 1983; [Transcription] (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Cooking and Living Along the River, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - List of Coffee County, Tennessee, Records, undated (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Eating to Live (blank), undated (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Editor and Publisher International Yearbook, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - The Eskridge Family, 1925 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - European Rail Guide, 2003-2004 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Family Reunions in the Great Smokies, 1993 Spring (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Federal Population Censuses, 1790-1890 Catalog, 1979, 1997-1999 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Franklin County, Tennessee, Abstracted Wills, 1808-1875, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Franklin County, Tennessee, Abstracted Wills, 1876-1891, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Franklin County, Tennessee, 1860 Census and Marriages for Head of Household, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Franklin County, Tennessee, Census, 1870; (Partial); [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 95, Folder 7] (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Franklin County, Tennessee, Court Minutes Abstracts (1832-1907), 1995 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Franklin County, Tennessee Court Minutes Index (1858-1879), undated; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 95, Folder 8] (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Franklin County, Tennessee Tax List (1852-1910), 1984; [Transcription] (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Franklin County, Tennessee 1890 Tax List, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Geographic Place Names in the Great Smoky Mountains National Park, 1978; (1 of 2) (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Geographic Place Names in the Great Smoky Mountains National Park, 1978; (2 of 2) (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - GoAhead Vacations Brochures, 2005-2006 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - 1880 Graham County, North Carolina, Census, 1994; [Transcription] (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Graham County Centennial, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Great Smoky Mountains Final Environmental Impact Statement General Management Plan, 1982 January; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 95, Folder 9] (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - The Great Smoky Mountains National Park, 1928 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Great Smoky Mountains National Park Personnel Directory (2 copies), 1990 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Great Smoky Mountains National Park Personnel Directory, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Greenbriar, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - 1810 Haywood County Census and 1809-1810 Haywood County Land Entries, undated; (Abstracts) (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Hazel Creek from Then Till Now, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - The Heart of the Alleghenies, 1883; (Partial) (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Hiking in the Great Smokies, 1962-1976 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Historic Hamblen, 1870-1970 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Historic Structures Report: Little Cataloochee, North Carolina, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - History of Mt. Sterling, NC ... and its People, 1996-2005 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - History of Mt. Sterling, NC ... and its People (Volume II), 1997-2005 (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - History of the Tennessee River Baptist Association for the Year 1830 to 1948 (Swain and Graham Counties, NC), undated (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Homesteads of the Great Smokies: A History of the Paynes and Related Families, 1992-1994 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Humble Vacation Guide: 50 Favorite Recreation Regions, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Index to Tennessee Confederate Pension Applications, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - 1860 Jackson County, North Carolina, Census, 1988; [Transcription] (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Dr. Joseph LeConte Autobiography, 1903, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - La memorie de la Vallee de Chamonix en cartes postales anciennes, 1999 December (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Abstracts of Wills, Lincoln County, Tennessee, 1810-1895, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Index to Lincoln County Court Records, 1974 May; (Partial) (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Local Registrar's Handbook on Birth, Death, and Fetal Death Registration (North Carolina), 1988 January (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Logging in the Great Smoky Mountains National Park, 1958 October 1 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Logging in the Great Smokies, 1880-1930, 1961 December (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Loudon County Men in 1891, 1995 Spring (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - 1830 Macon County, North Carolina, Census, undated; (Abstract) (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - 1840 Macon County, North Carolina, Census (Transcript), 2000 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - 1850 Macon County, North Carolina, Census (Transcript), 1987 April (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - The Map Store Catalog, undated (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Marshall County Court Records, 1974 July; (Partial Lists) (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Memories in the Smoky Mountains, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Memories of the Smokies, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Michael Frome Revisits Smokies, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - The Mirth of a National Park, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Moore County Court Records List, undated (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Morgan County Court Records List, 1975 April (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Mountain Roads and Quiet Places, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Newport, Tennessee Newspaper Clippings, 1881-1944; (1 of 3) (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Newport, Tennessee Newspaper Clippings, 1881-1944; (2 of 3) (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Newport, Tennessee Newspaper Clippings, 1881-1944; (3 of 3) (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - The Nomenclature of the Great Smoky Mountains, 1937 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - North Carolina v. Montvale Lumber Company, 1929 June 4-5 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - North Carolina Post Office Catalog (By County), undated; (1 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - North Carolina Post Office Catalog (By County), undated; (2 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - North Carolina Post Office Catalog (Alphabetical), (1 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - North Carolina Post Office Catalog (Alphabetical), (2 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - North Carolina Yearbook and Business Directory, 1902-1916 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Obituaries in Blount County, Tennessee Newspapers, 1878-1960, 1990; (Index); (1 of 3) (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Obituaries in Blount County, Tennessee Newspapers, 1878-1960, 1990; (Index); (2 of 3) (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Obituaries in Blount County, Tennessee Newspapers, 1878-1960, 1990; (Index); (3 of 3) (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Ocona Lufty Baptist: Pioneer Church of the Smokies, 1836-1939, 1990, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Official Guidebook to the Sequoyah Birthplace Museum, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Our Heritage: New Providence Presbyterian Church 1786-2000, undated (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - The Overmountain Men Program (copy), 1952 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - The Overmountain Press Catalog of Titles, 1999-2000 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - A Patchwork of Memories, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Pension Roll of 1835 (Transcript), 2000; (1 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Pension Roll of 1835 (Transcript), 2000; (2 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - A Piece of the Smokies: A Pictorial History of Life in the Smoky Mountains, undated (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Place Names of Tennessee, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - 1835 Poll books (North Carolina), 1988 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Post Offices and Postmasters Before the Great Smoky Mountains National Park, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Railroad Atlas of North America, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Ravensford, NC, 2002 June (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Remembered Lives: A Narrative History of Our Family, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 1)